<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Buckets Guide on Buckets</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/es/guide/</link><description>Recent content in The Buckets Guide on Buckets</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/es/guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>End User License Agreement</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/es/guide/eula/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/es/guide/eula/</guid><description>Effective as of September 23, 2022
Last Updated: Aug 30, 2023
Thank you for selecting Buckets! Please read this Agreement thoroughly. This Agreement is a legal agreement between you and Buckets. By clicking &amp;ldquo;I Agree&amp;rdquo; when prompted, or by installing, accessing or using the software, you agree to these terms. If you do not agree to this Agreement, then you may not use this software.
This Software Application End User License Agreement (the &amp;ldquo;Agreement&amp;quot;) is between you, the Customer (&amp;quot;User,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;you,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;your&amp;quot;) and One Part Rain, LLC, D/B/A Buckets, a Utah limited liability company (&amp;quot;Buckets,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;quot;).</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/es/guide/privacypolicy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/es/guide/privacypolicy/</guid><description>Effective as of September 23, 2022
This privacy policy (the &amp;ldquo;Privacy Policy&amp;quot;) applies to Buckets software application including content, updates and new releases (collectively, the &amp;ldquo;App&amp;quot;), owned and operated by One Part Rain, LLC, D/B/A Buckets (&amp;quot;Buckets,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;quot;). We have created this Privacy Policy to tell you what information the App collects, how we use that information, and who we will share that information with, if at all.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/es/guide/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/es/guide/faq/</guid><description>What limitations does the trial version have? The trial version of Buckets includes these limitations:
The app has a little yellow sticker in the bottom left side of the window Every budget will include a Buckets License bucket to help you save up for a license After a while, will periodically remind you to buy the full version. Otherwise, the trial version is identical to the full version.</description></item><item><title>File Format</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/es/guide/fileformat/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 11:36:13 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/es/guide/fileformat/</guid><description>NOTE: This article is intended for programmers who want to write programs that interface with budget files. You don't need this if you just want to use the Buckets app. Buckets budget files are SQLite databases. The schema is mostly self-explanatory, but this document points out some things that aren&amp;rsquo;t.
WARNING: The schema is not final and may change without warning in future versions of Buckets. If you still have questions after reading this, feel free to chat with me.</description></item></channel></rss>