<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Using Buckets on Buckets</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/</link><description>Recent content in Using Buckets on Buckets</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 11:36:13 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sharing</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/sharing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/sharing/</guid><description>Buckets currently supports sharing budget files between your devices in a one-way manner over the local network.
In the future, it will support two-way sharing both locally and across the Internet using your choice of the built in sync protocol or third party file-sharing services (e.g. Dropbox, Google Drive, iCloud, etc&amp;hellip;).
Sharing a budget with the mobile app Your mobile app and desktop computer must be on the same local network (e.</description></item><item><title>General</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/general/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/general/</guid><description>Saving Almost all changes you make in Buckets automatically save immediately. That&amp;rsquo;s why there&amp;rsquo;s no save button. Currently, the only exception to this is when recording macros (because updating macros must be explicitly saved).
Calculators Everywhere! Somewhat like a spreadsheet, every field in Buckets where you type in numbers is a calculator. For instance, you can type 2+2 or 35/12:
Notes Accounts, transactions, buckets and bucket groups can all have searchable notes attached to them.</description></item><item><title>Transactions</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/transactions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 13:08:44 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/transactions/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Buckets</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/buckets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 22:41:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/buckets/</guid><description>After entering our accounts, we clicked on the Buckets tab to divide up our money into useful categories—buckets. It&amp;rsquo;s useful to think of buckets as literal buckets, filled with money, sitting around your house (or pretend they&amp;rsquo;re envelopes, if you prefer).
We make a bucket for every independent expense or goal. We currently have 63 buckets, but we didn&amp;rsquo;t start with that many. Don&amp;rsquo;t feel pressured to make a bunch.</description></item><item><title>Accounts</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/accounts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 22:15:02 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/accounts/</guid><description>The very first thing we did when setting up our budget was to enter all our bank account names and balances in the Accounts tab.
Each account has a detailed view that you can get to by clicking more.
Naming accounts To name/rename an account, click on it&amp;rsquo;s name in the table (or in the detailed view) and type in the new name.
Balance In the account&amp;rsquo;s detailed view, change the balance by updating the value in the balance text box.</description></item><item><title>Categorizing</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/categorizing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 15:35:19 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/categorizing/</guid><description>Every real life transaction for your accounts should cause a corresponding transaction in one or more Buckets. So if you charged $1 to your credit card to buy a doughnut, you should take $1 out of your Doughnut bucket.
Also, if you don&amp;rsquo;t have one already, perhaps you should make a Doughnut bucket :)
Categorizing happens in the Transactions tab.
Simple categorizing Click Categorize on a transaction Choose a bucket from the dropdown menu.</description></item><item><title>Debt</title><link>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/debt/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 15:35:19 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.budgetwithbuckets.com/guide/app/debt/</guid><description>If you are trying to pay off debt, there are a few things Buckets can offer you.
Mortgage/Loan Many users treat fixed-payment credit (e.g. mortgages and car loans) as expenses to the budget rather than accounts within the budget. It makes sense to mark these kinds of debt accounts as Off Budget rather than Debt.
Credit Cards and Other Debt If you always pay off your credit card in full every statement, then you are safe to leave your credit card account as a Normal account.</description></item></channel></rss>